{
    "id": "2ffcb28c972e4a6a9b3a74a0d71eb821",
    "title": "Though, Although, Despite, In Spite Of",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She went out …………………. it was raining.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "in spite of",
                "despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "524cbf58d395499498e58dd6d117b268"
        },
        {
            "question": "The trains were late ………………… the rain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ee1d0e3aca19439a94b0bcd1aad69a23"
        },
        {
            "question": "I managed to arrive on time …………………. the train was late by an hour.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "although",
                "despite",
                "in spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "49d79df879464ee18e68fa7e7cfff651"
        },
        {
            "question": "I enjoyed the film …………………. having a headache.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "despite",
                "in spite of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c047fec4dded413bb234abd46c39a74d"
        },
        {
            "question": "She bought the car ………………… the fact that it was expensive.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "although",
                "because",
                "in spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "18703e5c6bee489ea489b1ed40e602ff"
        },
        {
            "question": "The dress was good …………….. expensive.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "despite",
                "however",
                "though"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "601e719de38c4be2b0b100fc74b2a177"
        },
        {
            "question": "John was absent. ……………….., everybody else was present.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "However",
                "Although"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4bc09b84c5f74e3f98cad0d366ea4716"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………….. John was absent, everybody else was present.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "However",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b4facdbe580c4f2f953ea251fd608903"
        },
        {
            "question": "We managed to do it ……………… we didn’t receive any assistance from them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "although",
                "however",
                "despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "380306ee06814b788b59d4da5216e3d2"
        },
        {
            "question": "We managed to do it ………………….. the fact that we didn’t receive any assistance from them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "however",
                "though",
                "despite"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d72c3434ee9d425a8a4c9d47e1fd6a62"
        }
    ]
}